Norton, Joseph L.; Papers ua902.006
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Faculty Papers, 1940-1983, Undated; 3; 5.6 cubic ft.
  - Student Work, 1947-1980, Undated; 3.2; 1.6 cubic ft.
    - Patrick Foti, 1970 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 24)
    - Nancy B. Guarelia, 1970 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 25)
    - Jim Hayes, 1970 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 26)
    - Practicum Critiques, 1970 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 27)
    - Ruth Pearson, 1970 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 28)
    - Lee Pierce, 1970 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 29)
    - Joseph Purcell, 1970 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 30)
    - Robert Swartz, 1970 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 31)
    - David Valle, 1970 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 32)
    - James Varelas, 1970 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 33)
    - Thomas Welliver, 1970 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 34)
    - Charles R. Britting, 1971 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 35)
    - Mark E. Hamdi, 1971 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 36)
    - Practicum Critiques, 1971 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 37)
    - Louis F. Saltrelli, 1971 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 38)
    - Shirley Zeitlin, 1971 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 39)
    - John C. Barner, 1972 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 40)
    - Clyde H. Eastman, 1972 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 41)
    - Marijane Hamilton Goyer, 1972; 1973; 1977 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 42)
    - Internship Evaluations, 1972 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 43)
    - Sally Ann Tschami, 1972 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 44)
    - Robert H. Suggs, 1973 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 45)
    - Elizabeth L. Burns, 1974 (Box 4 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 1)
    - Bruce A. Conroe, 1974 (Box 4 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 2)
    - John F. Covaleskie, 1974 (Box 4 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 3)
    - David Jenkins, 1974 (Box 4 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 4)
    - Ronald Kochis, 1974 (Box 4 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 5)
    - G. Geraldine Dickson, 1975 (Box 4 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 6)
    - James Gilmour, Arthur Jones, and Stephen Pattarini, 1975 (Box 4 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 7)
    - Lynn Golonka, 1975 (Box 4 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 8)
    - Harvey C. Huth, 1975 (Box 4 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 9)
    - Ross Thompson, 1975 (Box 4 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 10)
    - John Benson, 1976 (Box 4 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 11)
    - Artie Joseph, 1976 (Box 4 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 12)
    - Ronald Kochis, 1976 (Box 4 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 13)
    - Richard J. Musser, 1976 (Box 4 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 14)
    - Gail Coghlan, 1978 (Box 4 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 15)
    - Robert Giammatteo, 1978 (Box 4 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 16)
    - Brenda C. Russo, 1978 (Box 4 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 17)
    - Frederick Elliston, 1979 (Box 4 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 18)
    - Richard P. Cerniglia, Undated (Box 4 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 19)
    - Jihad N. Khatib, Undated (Box 4 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 20)
    - Rich Mucowski, Undated (Box 4 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 21)
    - Donald C. Wallace, Undated (Box 4 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 22)
  - University Service and Administrative Material, 1940-1983, Undated; 3.3; 2 cubic ft.
    This sub series contains the records of Joseph Norton's employment with and administration of the Department of Counseling and Personnel Services at SUNY Albany. This includes professional memberships and certifications, university service and committee records, employment records, official forms and documentation, and policy documents.
    - Personal Certification, 1940; 1946; 1954 (Box 4 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 23)
    - Syracuse University PhD Diploma, 1950 June (Box 4 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 24)
    - Education Programs, 1953 (Box 4 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 25)
    - Scientific Research Society of America, 1953 (Box 4 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 26)
    - Sigma Xi, 1953 (Box 4 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 27)
    - Holding Power, 1955 (Box 4 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 28)
    - Evaluations, 1956 (Box 4 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 29)
    - Alfred Tenure, 1959 (Box 4 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 30)
    - Annual Report Form, 1961; 1977; 1979; 1981 (Box 4 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 31)
    - Educational Psychology Doctoral Program, 1963 (Box 4 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 32)
    - Departmental Directions, 1963 (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 1)
    - Psychology Certificate, 1963 (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 2)
    - Cooperative Review Service, 1964 (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 3)
    - Guidance & Federal Funds, 1965 (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 4)
    - Janis Westervelt, 1965 (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 5)
    - Graduate Programs in Guidance, 1966 (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 6)
    - Albany Appointment, 1967 (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 7)
    - Curriculum Vitae, 1967; 1975; 1976; Undated (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 8)
    - Memorandum - Campus Master Plan, 1967 (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 9)
    - Preparation of Campus Academic Plans for 1968, 1967 (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 10)
    - Seminar 707, 1967 (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 11)
    - FASUNY, 1968 (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 12)
    - NDEA Proposal, 1968 (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 13)
    - Certification Proposal, 1969 (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 14)
    - Counceling Psychologists Commmittee, 1969 (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 15)
    - Convocation program, 1970 (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 16)
    - Evaluations, 1970 (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 17)
    - Certification List, 1970 (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 18)
    - Guidelines and Forms, 1970; 1971; 1974 (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 19)
    - Master Plan Symposium Papers, 1970 (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 20)
    - Personnel Data Forms, 1970; 1971; 1972; 1976 (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 21)
    - Seminar Dissertation Procedures, 1970 (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 22)
    - Staff response to Certification, 1970 (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 23)
    - Student Evaluations, 1970; Undated (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 24)
    - Dissertation, 1971; 1976; Undated (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 25)
    - Doctoral Dissertation Committee, 1971 (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 26)
    - Psychology Department and Course Evaluation Summaries, 1971 (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 27)
    - Admissions Committee, 1972 (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 28)
    - Committee to Improve Instruction, 1972 (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 29)
    - Comprehensive Examinations, 1972 (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 30)
    - Evaluations, 1972 (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 31)
    - Guidelines for Campus Master Plans, 1972 (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 32)
    - Master Planning Symposium Papers (additional information), 1972 (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 33)
    - Revised Program Leading to the University Certificate in Counseling and Personnel Services, 1972 (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 34)
    - SUNY Albany DCPS Doctoral Program, 1972 (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 35)
    - Counseling Curriculum Group, 1973 (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 36)
    - Guidelines to Internships, 1973; Undated (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 37)
    - Student Appraisal of Counseling Instruction (SACI), 1973 (Box 5 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 38)
    - Student Appraisal of Counseling Instruction (SACI), 1973 (Box 6 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 1)
    - Student Appraisal of Counseling Instruction (SACI) Evaluations, 1973 (Box 6 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 2)
    - Coffey's Proposal, 1974 (Box 6 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 3)
    - Course Evaluations, 1974 (Box 6 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 4)
    - Dissertation Seminar Committee, 1974 (Box 6 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 5)
    - Educational Psychology, 1974 (Box 6 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 6)
    - Sabatical Leave, 1974 (Box 6 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 7)
    - Student Appraisal of Counseling Instruction (SACI), 1974 (Box 6 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 8)
    - Department Chairman Job Description, 1975 (Box 6 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 9)
    - Admissions - Department of Counseling and Personnel Services, 1976 (Box 6 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 10)
    - Community University Day, 1977 (Box 6 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 11)
    - Computing Center, 1977 (Box 6 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 12)
    - Department of Counseling and Personnel Services, 1977 (Box 6 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 13)
    - Department of Counseling and Personnel Services - Advisement, 1977 (Box 6 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 14)
    - Department of Counseling and Personnel Services - Courses, 1977 (Box 6 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 15)
    - Ed.S Program in Counseling, 1977; Undated (Box 7 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 1)
    - Doctoral Dissertations, 1978 (Box 7 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 2)
    - Department of Counseling and Personnel Services - By-laws, 1979 (Box 7 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 3)
    - Doctoral Program Extension, 1979 (Box 7 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 4)
    - Liberal Education, 1979 (Box 7 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 5)
    - Minutes of the Two-Year Program Committee, 1979 (Box 7 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 6)
    - Retention, 1979 (Box 7 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 7)
    - Salaries, 1979 (Box 7 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 8)
    - Advisement Assignment, 1981 (Box 7 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 9)
    - Department of Counseling and Personnel Services - By-laws, 1981 (Box 7 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 10)
    - Independent Study, 1981 (Box 7 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 11)
    - Student Instructional Rating Form, 1981 (Box 7 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 12)
    - Subaccounts, 1981 (Box 7 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 13)
    - Academic Program Council, 1982 (Box 7 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 14)
    - New York State Psychological Association, 1982 (Box 7 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 15)
    - Sabbatical Leave, 1982 (Box 7 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 16)
    - Current Year Activities, 1983 (Box 7 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 17)
    - Doctoral Applications, Undated (Box 7 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 18)
    - Educational Innovation, Undated (Box 7 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 19)
    - "Incidences of Insanity" talk note cards, Undated (Box 7 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 20)
    - Materials for use in counseling lesbian and gay men, Undated (Box 7 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 21)
- Subject Files, 1946-ca. 1996, Undated; 4; 5.4 cubic ft.
  - Activism, 1970-ca. 1996, Undated; 4.1; 0.6 cubic ft.
    Includes the documentation of Joseph Norton's politcal activism and promotion of Gay rights
    - AASECT, ca. 1980 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
    - Aging Gays, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
    - Albany Gay Lib History 1979 List, Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
    - Bicentennial Conference on the Gays and the Federal Government, 1976 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
    - Capital District Gay Community Council - press release, 1984 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
    - Capital District Gay Political Caucus and New York State Coalitions of Gay Organizations, 1978; 1980 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
    - "Come Out!" Gay Liberation Front Newsletter, 1970 (Oversized 1, Folder 1)
    - Early Interweave, 1993; 1994; 1995; 1996 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
    - Gay Activism, 1970; 1973 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
    - Gay Activists Alliance, Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
    - Gay Awareness and Identity, 1972; 1973; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
    - Gay phone numbers, New York State, Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
    - Gay Rights National Lobby, 1981; 1982 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
    - Gay Rights National Lobby, 1981; 1982; 1983 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
    - Gay Rights National Lobby, 1981-1983 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
    - Gay Rights National Lobby, 1983; 1984 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
    - International Gay Organizations, 1982; 1983 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
    - March on Albany, SUNY Albany Gay and Lesbian Alliance, Lesbian and Gay People of New York State, New York State Coalition of Gay Organizations, 1980; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
    - National Activist Union of Gays and Lesbians, 1978-1981 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
    - National Coalition of Black Gays, 1979 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
    - National Coalition of Black Gays, grant request, ca. 1979 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
    - National Coalition of Black Gays, National Gay Task Force, Human Dignity Fund, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
    - National Gay Archives, 1982 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
    - National Gay Health Coalition, 1981 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
    - National Gay Health Conference, 1978 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24)
    - National Gay Task Force, 1973; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
    - National Gay Task Force, 1979 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
    - National Gay Task Force, directory, Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27)
    - National March on Washington for Lesbian and Gay Rights, 1979 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28)
    - New York State Coalition of Gay Organizations (NYSCOGA) - meeting minutes, 1971 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 29)
    - New York State Gay and Lesbian Conference, 1983 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 30)
    - New York State Lesbian & Gay Lobby, 1982; 1983; 1984; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 31)
    - New York State Lesbian & Gay Lobby, By-laws, 1984; 1985 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 32)
    - New York State Lesbian and Gay Political Alliance, 1981 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 33)
    - Joseph Norton presentation on S&M, ca. 1996 (Oversized 1, Folder 2)
    - NYSPGA, Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 34)
    - Statement before legislative hearing, 1971 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 35)
    - SUNY Alfred, Gay Liberation Front, 1973 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 36)
    - Two Rivers, 1989; 1990; 1991 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 37)
    - Unitarian Universalist Gay and Lesbian Material, 1974-1976; 1981; 1986; 1988; 1991 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 38)
    - Unitarian Universalist Lesbian & Gay Caucus - By-laws committee, 1984; 1986 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 39)
    - Unitarian Universalist mailing lists, 1978-1981 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Correspondence, 1951-1980, Undated; 4.2; 0.5 cubic ft.
    Alphabetical by correspondent or subject
    Consists of Joseph Norton's correspondence throughout his professional career
    - A, 1951; 1964-1965; 1968-1978; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 41)
    - Aunt Nellie, 1961-1963; 1965 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 42)
    - B, 1953; 1961; 1963-1967; 1970; 1973-1979 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 43)
    - C, 1951; 1954; 1963-1968; 1973-1979 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 44)
    - Class of 1940, 1957-1962 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 45)
    - Class of 1940, 1959-1974 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 46)
    - D, 1957-1958; 1963; 1967-1968; 1975-1977 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 47)
    - Draft Board, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 48)
    - E, 1963; 1964 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 49)
    - F, 1958; 1962; 1964; 1966-1967; 1999 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 50)
    - G, 1963; 1965; 1967-1968; 1970-1976; 1979 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 51)
    - Joseph Gentilini, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 52)
    - H, 1946; 1952-1953; 1958; 1963-1967; 1970-1980 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 53)
    - I, 1975 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 54)
    - J, 1961; 1963; 1970; 1972-1973; 1975 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 55)
    - K, 1967; 1972; 1973; 1975; 1977 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 56)
    - L, 1958; 1965-1968; 1971; 1973; 1976-1977 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 57)
    - M, 1951-1958; 1963-1967; 1969-1970; 1972-1977; 1979 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 58)
    - Richard Mombello, 1978 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 59)
    - N, 1960 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 60)
    - Norge, 1962 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 61)
    - Estate of Jessie V. S. Norton, 1962; 1963 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 62)
    - O, 1964; 1967 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 63)
    - P, 1951-1955; 1959; 1961-1967; 1970-1972; 1983 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 64)
    - Personal Material, 1961; 1964; 1965; Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 65)
    - Phi Delta Kappan, 1977 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 66)
    - R, 1957; 1966-1967; 1977; 1979 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 67)
    - S, 1952-1953; 1957; 1962-1968; 1971-1977; 1981 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 68)
    - Sailboats, 1955; 1966 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 69)
    - Samuel Stratton, Jacob K. Javits, 1980 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 70)
    - Summer Jobs, 1968-1970 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 71)
    - T, 1961; 1965-1967; 1973 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
    - U, 1962 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
    - University of British Columbia, 1964-1966 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
    - Queens College - institute for vocational guidance, 1965 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
    - V, 1976; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
    - W, 1957; 1961-1966; 1969-1972; 1976; 1979-1980 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
    - Workshop - Teacher's College, Columbia University, 1967 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
    - Y, 1978 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Reference Material, 1946-1991, Undated; 4.3; 4.3 cubic ft.
    Consists of research and informational material held by Joseph Norton to be used for reference.
    - Abuse, 1977; 1988 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
    - Access to Pupil Records, 1960; 1961 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
    - ACES-ASCA policy statement on school conselors, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
    - Achievement, 1949; 1961 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
    - Action - training through sociodrama, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
    - Addresses, mailing history, 1955; 1978; 1979; 1980; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
    - Aesthetic Realism, ca. 1977 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
    - Agencies to visit for 614-669, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
    - Alcohol Education & Alcoholism, 1959-1961 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
    - American Personnel and Guidance Association, 1979; 1980 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
    - Amids, 1973 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
    - Association for Gay, Lesbian, and Bisexual Issues in Counceling, 1999 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
    - Attendance Teachers, 1963 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
    - Behavior Modification, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
    - Behavioral Therapy, 1966-1967; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
    - Biographical Collections, 1969-1974; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24)
    - Birth Control, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
    - Birth Trauma, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
    - Black Gays, 1979 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27)
    - Black Vocabulary, 1970 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28)
    - Black & White Students Interaction with Councelors, 1970 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 29)
    - Body Pleasure and the origins of violence, 1975 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 30)
    - By-Laws, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 31)
    - Candidates for Certification, 1970; 1971; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 32)
    - Capital District Council on Human Sexuality, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 33)
    - Career Assessment Inventory Results, 1978 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 34)
    - Career Counseling, 1970; 1975; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 35)
    - Career Information, 1950; 1963; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 36)
    - Career Inslights and Self Awareness Gaming, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 37)
    - Career Planning, 1975 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 38)
    - Change of Address, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 39)
    - Child Management Techniques, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 40)
    - Child-Rearing, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 41)
    - Childhood Sexuality, 1978; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 42)
    - Clippings, 1966; 1972; 1978; 1979; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 43)
    - Clothing, 1968 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 44)
    - College Appications, 1954; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 45)
    - Community Mental Health, 1958; 1960; 1964; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 46)
    - "Community"- newsletter of the Capital District Gay Commuity Council, 1973 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 47)
    - Conflicts in Society, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 48)
    - Conforming, 1965 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 49)
    - Contraception and menstration, 1969; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 50)
    - Contract Psychology, 1964 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 51)
    - Correspondence and reference material on transgender issues, 1973; 1977; 1990; 1999; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 52)
    - Counseling glossary, 1962 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 53)
    - Counseling & Guidance Institute, Central Washington College, 1961 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 54)
    - Counseling institute in an oppressive environment, 1974 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 55)
    - Counseling News and Views, 1950 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 56)
    - Counseling Scenarios, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 57)
    - Counselor's Day, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 58)
    - Counselor Education, 1971 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 59)
    - Counselor Education, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 60)
    - Counselor Education Meetings, 1956 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 61)
    - Counselor's Self-Concept, 1958-1966 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 62)
    - Counselor Preparation, 1960-1969 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 63)
    - Counselor Preparation, 1960-1969 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 64)
    - Creativity, 1961; 1963-1965; 1969; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 65)
    - Crisis intervention procedure, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 66)
    - Critique of "Mormonism and the Negro", Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 67)
    - Delinquency, 1955; 1958; 1962; 1964; Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 68)
    - Delinquency, 1953-1954; 1957; 1966-1967; Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
    - Delinquency, 1956-1959; 1962; 1965; Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
    - Delinquency, 1964; 1965; Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
    - Deinstitutionalization, 1978 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
    - Diet and Health, 1974; Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
    - Dissertation Costs, 1971 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
    - Dissertation Procedure, 1969 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
    - Doc Cop, 1975 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
    - Draft Counseling, 1970 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
    - Drugs, 1973; 1974; 1976; 1977; Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
    - Educational Interest Survey, 1962 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
    - Effects of Sleep Suggestions on Specific Personality Traits, ca. 1958 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
    - Elementary Guidance, 1964 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
    - ESP, 1967; Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
    - Ethics, 1956-1957; 1969; Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
    - Evaluations of Guidance Counselors and Their Programs, 1953-1961 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
    - Evangelicals Concerned, 1981-1982 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)